Inventory of the Gordon Leo McDonough papers 0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
- File of CASES
  - File of CASES, 1950/59
    - Mc Donough Bills renge Hr 48- 2560 85th Congress I Session, 1957
    - McDonough press releases, 1955
    - Bills (arrnged by bill nr.) 84th Congress I session, 1955
    - Record of McDonough 86 Congress 1st Session, 1959
    - House Resolutions introduced 93rd Congress
  - File Cases, 1951/53
    arranged aphabetical by subject headers in folders
    - Agriculture, Jan. 1951 (Box Box CASES 24)
    - Agriculture Department, Jan. 1952
    - Airforce, Jan. 1951
    - Airforce, Jul. 1951
    - Atomic Energy, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Banking Currency Committee, 1951-1952
    - Central Intelligence, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Civil Rights, Jan. 1951
    - Civil Rights, Jan. 1951
    - Federal Trade Commission, Jan. 1951
    - General Accounting Office, Jan. 1951
    - General Accounting Office, Jan. 1952
    - General Service Administration, Jan. 1951
    - General Service Administration, Jan. 1952
    - Housing, 1951-'52
    - Immigration, 1951
    - Income Tax, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Internal Revenue, Bureau of Jan. 1951
    - Interior Department, Jan. 1951
    - Interstate Commission, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Labor Department, 1951
    - Labor Department, 1952
    - Library of Congress
    - Maritime Commission, Jan. 1951
    - Mobilazation, 1951-1952
    - National Guard, Jan. 1951-1952
    - National Labor Relations Board, Jan. 1951
    - National Production Authority, Jan. 1951
    - National Production Authority, Jan. 1952
    - National Science Foundation, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Navy, 1951
    - Office of Price Stabilization, 1951
    - Patent Cases, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Political Appoitment Request, Jan. 1951
    - Post Office Department, Jan. 1951
    - Rent Control, Jan. 1951
    - Rent Control, Jan. 1952
    - Selective Service, Jan. 1951
    - Selective Service, Jan 1952
    - Small Business, Jan. 1951-1952
    - Social Security, Jan. 1951
    - State Department, July 1951
    - Treasury Department, Jan. 1951
    - War Claims, Jan. 1951
    - War Claims, Jan. 1952
  - File of CASES, 1953
    aphabetically by Subject headers in folders
    - Agriculture Dept., Jan.- (Box Box CASES 25)
    - Air Force Dept., July -
    - Air Force, Jan. -June
    - Army Dept, Jan.-
    - Army Dept., April-June
    - Army, July
    - Atom Energy, Jan.-
    - Census Burea, Jan.-
    - Civil Service Commission, Jan.-
    - Civil Aerorautics Board, July -
    - Commerce Dept., Jan.-
    - Committee Hearing, May -
    - Defense Dept., Jan. -
    - D.C. (District of Columbia), Jan.-
    - Economic Stablization Commission, Jan.-
    - General Accounting Office, Jan.-
    - General Services Administration, Jan.-
    - Immigration, July -
    - Immigration, Jan. thr. June
    - Internal revenue, Jan.-
    - Interior Dept., Jan.-
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, Jan.-
    - Navy Dept., Jan.-
    - P. P. Dept., Jan.-
    - Rent Control, Jan.-
    - Railroad Retirement, Jan.-
    - Selective Service Board, Jan.53
    - State Dept., Jan.-
    - State Dept., April-June
    - State Dept., July-
    - U.N(United Nations), Jan.-
    - U.S. Employment Compensation, Jan.-
    - Veterans Adminstration, April-June
    - Veterans Administration, July-
    - War Claims Commission, Jan.-
    - West Coast Shipyards
  - File of Cases, 1954
    aphabetically by Subject headres in manilla enveloppes
    - Agriculture Dept. (Box Box CASES 26)
    - Air Forca Dept.
    - Alien Property
    - Army Dept.
    - Banking
    - Census Burea
    - Civil Aeronautics
    - Civil Service Commission
    - Commerce Dept.
    - Committee Hearing
    - Defense Dept.
    - Federal Communication Commission
    - Federal Housing Commission
    - Flag cese
    - F.O.A. (Foreign Operations Administration)
    - GeneralAccounting Office
    - General Contract
    - General Services Administration
    - Housing
    - Indian Affairs
    - Internal Revenue Burea
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Justice Dept.
    - Labor Dept.
    - Maritime Commission
    - Mutual Security Adminstration
    - Patent Office
    - Post Office Dept.
    - Public Works
    - Navy Dept.
    - Rail Road Retirement
    - Selective Service Board
    - Small Business Administrtion
    - Small Business Committee
    - Social Security Administration
    - State Dept.
    - Treasury cases
    - Veterans Administration
    - War Claims Commission
  - File of CASES, 1954/56
    Arr. by Subject aphabetically in manilla enveloppes folders
    - Agriculture Dept. H R6382 (People Timber report), Jan- 1956 (Box Box CASES 27)
    - Airforce (Kingsley Stamping Machine), 1954, '53
    - Army Dept., July-1955
    - Army folder HeatonCowie, Jan- 1956 1955, '53 '52
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, Jan-1956
    - Civil Service Commission, Jan-1955
    - Commerce Dept., Jan-1956
    - Customs, 1956
    - Daggett, 1954
    - Defence Dept., Jan-1965, '55
    - District of Columbia, 1956
    - Federal Communications Commissie, Jan-1956
    - Federal Housing Administration, Jan-1956 '55
    - Federal Trade Commission, Jan-1956
    - Flag, Jan-1956
    - General Accounting Office, Jan-1955
    - General Services Administration, Jan-1956
    - Housing, Jan-1956
    - Indian Affairs H R 4367 P law 887, Jan-1956
    - Interior Dept., Jan-1956, '55
    - Internal Revenue Bureau, Jan- 1956, '55
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, Jan-1956
    - International Cooperation Adminstration (ICA), 1956
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1956
    - Justice Dept., Jan-1956, '55
    - Labor Dept., Jan-1956
    - Maritime Commission, Jan-1955
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), Jan-1956, '55
    - National Archives, Jna-1955
    - Navy Dept., July-1955
    - Navy Dept., Jan-1956
    - Patent Office, Jan-1955
    - Patent Office, Jan-1956
    - Post Office, Jan-June 1955, '54
    - Post Office Dept., Jan-1956
    - Small Business Administration (Bus. loans application by regions, Jan-1956 1956)
    - Small Business Committee, Jan-1956
    - Social Security Administration, Jan-1956, '55
    - State Dept. H R 7742, Jan-June 1955, '54
    - State Dept. H R 2787 (Relieft of Moncado), Jan-1956, '55
    - U S Employment Compensation, Jan. 1955
    - Veterans, Jan-June 1955
    - Veterans Administration, July-1955
    - War Claims Commission, Jan-1955
    - Selective Service Board, Jan-1956
    - Newspaper file
  - File of CASES, 1955/56
    Arr. by subject in manilla enveloppes folders
    - Agriculture Dept., Jan- 1955 (Box Box CASES 28)
    - Airforce, Jan- June 1955
    - Airforce Dept., Jan- 1956
    - Airforce Dept., July-1955
    - Alien Property Custodian, Jan- 1955
    - Army, Jan-June 1955
    - Army Dept., July-1955
    - Central Intelligence Agency, Jan-1955
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, Jan-1955
    - Civil Service Commission, Jan-1955
    - Civil Service Commission, Jan-1956
    - Defense Dept., Jan-1955
    - Federal Communication, Jan-1955
    - Federal Housings Administration, Jna- 1955,'54
    - Federal Trade Commission, Jan- 1955, '54
    - Flag, Jan- 1955
    - Foreign Operations Administration, Jan- 1955, '54
    - General Accounting Office, Jan- 1955
    - General Services Administration, Jan-1955
    - Health, Education Welfare, Jan-1955
    - Housing, Jan-1955, '54
    - Immigration Dept., Jan-1956
    - Immigration Dept. (refugee act 1953 as amended), Jan-1955, '54
    - Indian Affairs, Jan-1955
    - Interior Dept., Jan 1955
    - Internal Revenue Bureau Public Law 585, Jan-1955
    - Justice Dept. (Finn Twins), Jan-1955, '54
    - Labor Dept., Jan-1955
    - Maritime Commission, Jan-1955
    - National Archives, Jan-1955
    - National Labor Relations Board, Jan 1955, '54
    - Navy, Jan-June 1955, '54
    - Post Office Dept., July-1955
    - Public Health Service, Jan- 1955
    - Public Lands, Jan-1955
    - Railroad Retirement, Jan-1955
    - Selective Service Board, Jan-1955
    - Small Business Administration, Jan-1955
    - Small Business Committee, Jan-1955, '54
    - Social Securuty Administration, Jan-1955
    - State Dept., July-1955
    - Tariff Commission, Jan-1955, '54
    - Tariff Commission, Jan-1956
    - Treasury Dept., Jan-1955
    - Treasury Dept., Jan-1956
    - U S Employment H R 1202 (compensation), Jan-1956
    - Veterans, Ja-June 1955
    - Veterans Administration, Jan-1956, '55
    - Home Loans Bank Board, Jan-1955
    - Commerce Dept., Jan- 1955, '54
    - War Claims Commission Public Law 285, Jan-1956
  - File of CASES 85th Congress, 1957 1958
    alphabetical by Subject in manillan enveloppes
    - Agriculture, 1957-'58 (Box Box CASES 29 30)
    - Airforce Department, 1958
    - Archives, Jan- '57
    - Army, 1957, '58
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1958
    - Banking, 1958
    - California Un-employed, 1958
    - Census, 1957 -, '58
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1957 - '58
    - Civil Defence, 1957
    - Civil Service, Jan -1957
    - Civil Service, Jan -1958
    - Commerce, Jan -1957
    - 1957-, '58
    - Defence Dept., Jan -1957
    - Defence Dept., 1958
    - Emigration, 1957, '58
    - Federal Communications Commission, Jan- 1957
    - Federal Housing Administration, Jan- 1957
    - Federal Trade Commission, Jan- 1957
    - Food Drug, Jan- 1957
    - General Services Administration, 1957
    - Housing, 1957, '58
    - Indian Affairs, 1957, '58
    - Interior Dept., 1957, '58
    - Internal Revenue, 1957, '58
    - International Cooperation Administration (ICA), 1957, '58
    - Justice Dept., 1957, '58
    - Labor Dept., 1957, '58
    - Maritime Commissions, 1957, '58
    - Navy Dept., 1957, '58
    - Patent Office, 1957, '58
    - Post Office, Jan- 1957
    - Post Office Dept., Jan-1957
    - Public Health, 1958
    - Selective Service, 1957, '58
    - Small Business Administration, Jan - 1957, '58
    - Social Security, Jan-1957
    - Social Security, 1958
    - State Dept.box 30, Jan-1957
    - State Dept., 1958
    - Tariff, 1957, '58
    - Treasury Dept., 1957, '58
    - U.S.Employee's Compensation, 1957
    - U.S. Employee Compansation, 1957, '58
    - Veterans, Jan- 1957
    - Veterans, Jan- 1958
  - File of CASES 86th CONGRESS, 1959 Jan -
    aphabetical by SUBJECT in folders
    - Agriculture (Box Box CASES 31)
    - Airforce
    - Army
    - Atomic Energy
    - Banking
    - Census
    - Civil Aeronautics Board
    - Civil Service
    - Coast Guard
    - Commerce
    - Customs
    - D.C. (District of Columbia)
    - Defence Department
    - F.C.C. (Federal Communications Comm.)
    - F.H.A. (Federal Housing Administration)
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - G.A.O. (General Accounting Office)
    - G.S.A. (General Services Administartion)
    - Housing
    - I.C.A. (International Cooperations Adminsitration)
    - I.C.C. (Interstate Commerce Commission)
    - Immigration
    - Indian Affairs
    - Internal Revenue
    - Interior Department
    - Interstate Commerce
    - Justice Dept.
    - Labor Dept.
    - Maritime Commission
    - Navy Dept.
    - Patent Office
    - Post Office
    - R.R. Ret. (Railroad Retirement Board)
    - Security Exchange Commission
    - Selective service
    - Small Business Administration
    - Social Security
    - State Department
    - Treasury Dept.
    - Veterans Administration
    - U.S. Employee Compensation
    - War Claims
    - World Bank
  - File of CASES, 1960 Jan. -
    arranged aphabetical by SUBJECT in folders
    - Agriculture (Box Box CASES 32)
    - Airforce
    - Army
    - Banking
    - Census Applications
    - Census Bureau
    - Civil Aeronautic Board
    - Civil Service
    - Defense Dept.
    - Export- Import Bank
    - Federal Aviation Agency
    - Federal Communications Commission (F.C.C.)
    - Federal Housing Administration (F.H.H.)
    - Fifty Star Flag
    - Food Drug Administration
    - General Services Administration
    - Heath, Education Welfare
    - Housing
    - Indian Affairs
    - Immigration
    - Interior Dept.
    - Internal Revenue
    - Justice Dept.
    - Maritime Commission
    - Navy
    - Patent Office
    - Post Office Dept.
    - Security Exchange Commission
    - Selective Service
    - Small Business
    - Space (Nat. Aeronautics Space Administration
    - Social Security
    - State Dept.
    - Tariff Commission
    - Treasury Dept.
    - U.S. Employee Compensation
    - Veterans
    - War Claims
  - FILE ofCASES, 1961/62
    arranged aphabetically by subjects A thr. I in folders
    - A. E.C. Atomic Energy Commission, 1961 (Box Box CASES 33)
    - Agriculture, 1961, '62
    - Airforce, Jan. 1962
    - Archives, 1960, '62
    - Army, Jan. 1962, '61
    - Banking, 1961, '60 '62
    - Census, Jan. 1961 '62
    - Civil Defense, 1962
    - Civil Service, Jan. 1961, '62
    - Civil Service, 1962
    - Commerce, 1962
    - Commerce, 1962
    - Coast Guard, Jan. 1961, '62
    - Defence Dpt, Jan. 1961, '62
    - Education, 1962
    - Favor, Jan. 1962
    - Favor, April 1962
    - Favor, August 1962
    - Favor White House Tour, 1961, '62
    - Federal Communication Commission, 1961, '62
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1961, '62
    - Federal Aviation Agency, 1961
    - Food Drug, 1961
    - General Accounting Office GAO, 1961, '62
    - General Services Administration GSA, 1961, '62
    - Glenn
    - Health, Education Welfare HEW, 1961, '62
    - Housing, 1961, '62
    - International Cooperation Administration ICA, 1960, '61
    - Immigration, 1961, '60 '62
    - Internal Revenue, 1961, '62
    - Indian Affairs, 1961, '62
    - Indian Affairs ADAMS, 1961
    - Interior Dpt., 1961, '60
    - Interior Dpt., 1962
  - File of CASES, 1961
    Arranged aphabetical by SUBJECT
    - Airforce, Jan-'61 (Box Box CASES 34)
    - Army, Jan-'61
    - Navy, Jan-61
    - Postoffice, '61
    - State Department, '61
    - Veterans, '61
    - Legislation introduced by McDonough 81st Congr. 1st Session, 1949
    - McDonough Bills 81st Congress 1st Session, 1949
    - McDonough Bills 82nd Congress 1st Session, 1951
    - Record of McDonough 81st Congress 1st Session, 1949
    - Record of McDonough 82nd Congress 2nd Session, 1950
  - File of CASES, 1960 1961 1962
    arrnged alphabetical by SUBJECT
    - Gianivos, 1962 (Box Box CASES 35)
    - Interior Dept. (moran), 1960, '59
    - Justice Dept., 1961
    - Labor Dept., Jan-1961, '62
    - Merchant Marine, 1960, '61'62
    - National Guaerd, 1961
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLB), 1961
    - Navy, Jan-1962
    - Patent Office, Jan-1961, '62
    - Peace Corps, 1962
    - Post Office, Jan-1962
    - Public Health, 1961
    - Railroad Retirement R R T), 1961, '62
    - Security Excgange Commission, 1961, '62
    - Selective Service, 1961, '62
    - Small Business, Jan-1961, '62
    - Social Security Morales, 1962, '61
    - Social Security, 1961, '62
    - Space, 1962
    - State Dept., Jan-1962
    - Treasure Dept., 1961, '62
    - Un-American Activities Commission, 1961
    - Un-employment Compensation, 1961, '62
    - U. S. Employee Compensation, 1961, '62
    - Veterans, Jan-1962
    - War Claims, 1961, '62
    - Yugoslavia (JETS), 1961
- File of COMMITTEES
  - File of COMMITTEES, 1945-1950
    in folders with headers
    Arranged aphabetically according to headers in Boxes 36 - 39
    - PUBLIC WORKS COMMITTEES, 1947 (Box Box COMM. 36)
      - Public buildings lands subcommittee Public Law 601 H R 1106 2086 2771 3029 3030 3072
        (Acquisition of site U S court of appeals district courts for district of Columbia building for GAO, construction new Federal buildins in L A, erecting public buildings in Andrews S. Carolina, FWA report on plan preperation of State Local public works, hearin on HR 3072 310 H J RES 164, Public Works Administration, maps, proposed site plans, proposed L A Civic Center)
      - Public buildings lands subcommittee H R 6328 6332 (Construction of Custom House, Federal buildings project descriptions, legislative calendar 80 Congrees '48, committe on Public Works), 1947-48
        (Advanced planning program, American Public Power Association, distribution of electric power generated at reservoir projects, federal projects approved under Lanham act, industrial wastes [UNK] legislative reorganisation act, listings of bills Committees 79 Congress '47, report on plan preperation of state local Public Works, veterans educational facilities program, legislative calendars April '47 May '47)
    - PUBLIC WORKS COMMITTEE
      - Beach erosion subcommittee (Bulletin of beach erosion board, fedral participation in constructing protective works against shore line erosion, flood control, port Hueneme erosion, shore line development L A county, 1947-48
      - Beach erosion subcommittee Public Law 166 727 H R 2032 2033, 1947
        (Beach erosion studies, beach erosion board studies, bulletin of beach erosion board, erosion along atlantic north shores of Long Island, ersosion Seal beach Surfside, fedral participation costs protecting shores of publicly owned property, general shore line investigation at fedral expense, San Pedro bay maps)
    - BEACH EROSION SUB*COMMITTEE PC W (federal partipocation in costs protecting shores publicly owned property, lists of parties, public hearings L A, public notice shore protection report, Port Huenema area) Public Law 166 520 525 727, 1949
    - BIXBY SLOUGH (connection West Basin with Bixbyslough, expansion LA harbor, L A harbor Company map, list of parties, public hearings, Nigger Slough Basin, US engeneerin Office, War department), 1945-'49
    - DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA H R 322 324 326 480 995 2405 2565 2875 3367 3306 S 125 1426 (abolish U S park police force in D C, district of Columbia redevellopment, fix salaries officers Metropolitan police fire dept., land tranfer for park purposes, legislative calender 79 Congress, personal of park service tranfer to Metropolitan Police Dept., prohibit issuance alcoholic beverages prcing, adverting, Slum clearnce bill, teachers salary bill, establish Met. Police Dept band, public low rent housing, Mc Donough folder), 1945-46
    - P W C FLOOD CONTROL (sub cooittee chaiman), 1948
    - P W C FLOOD CONTROL Public Law 573 601 (Compton creek, general plan flood control, 108th Street ditch), 1947 '48
    - FLOOD CONTROL Sub-commity (Ass. of Western States Engeneers resolution, drainagearea projects, L A flood control district, (county), low -priced housing Westwood-Sawtell project, public hearings, public hearings on flood control projects, REBER plan-San Francisce Bay erea project, San Antono dam, Tuolumne river, Whittier Narrows), 1947-49
      Flood Control projects in California
    - PUBLIC ROADE P W C
      - sub-commity (American Ass. Of State Highway officials Re. I, problem of highway vehicle size weight), 1949
    - RIVER HARBORS PWC
      - sub-committee H R 1949 4568 (Big Sandy Canal project, Big Sandy River water way, Bixby Slough Laguna Dominguez improving, Redondo beach harbor.)
    - PUBLIC BUILDINGS L A P W C, 1948
      (building record construction industry in California, conference Civic Center Authority of city LA, terminal annex building)
    - CUSTOMS NEEDS SERVICE, 1948 '49
      Private Law 900 (condemnation Duntley building, foreign trade association, U S Appraiser's Office)
    - PUBLIC WORKS COMMITTEE
      - Rivers Harbors sub-committee H R 123 315 470 6407 S 418 (Barkley Taft stream improvement bill, National Reclamation Association-bills-projects-forecasts-members committee sub committee Oxnard harbor district, report River Harbor bill, stream pollution, water supply forecast Columbia River System), 1947
      - Rivers Harbors sub-committee S 418 S J RES III H J RES 192 194, 1947-48
        (Arkansas river multiple purpose plan, Barkley Taft, Harbor for ligt draft vessels-public notice, pollution control bill, St Lawrence project maps, War Dept. examination coast south. California, War Dept reports harbors: Forida, Maine, Massachusetts, Michigan, New York, Oregon, Texas, Virginia)
        (Committee on public works:reports for: Maryland, Massachusetts, North Carolina, Oregon, Rhode Island)
    - PUBLIC WORKS HR 30363580 6332 S 1306 RES 6377, 1947-48
      (Aqueduct construstion metropolitan water district of South California, Dept. of Army, flood control, highways legislative history 18 Congress '48, listing of school district buildings facilities '48, stream pollution, St Laweence project, Whittier Narrows dam)
    - PUBLIC WORKS COMMITTE HR 3036 3490 S J III Punlic Law 485 (Basilone housing project, central valley project of California '41, interstate oil pipeline network, legislative calender 18 Congress '47, soil conservation districts, terminal island naval shipyard employees association), 1947
    - PUBLIC WORKS COMMITTEE HR 533 3086 5139 5472 6281 (construction repair public works on rivers harbors for navigation flood control, hearings committee public works 81 Congress '49, improvements Capital power plant-report architects, Kaplan Co. Sun Steel Company scrap steel, missouri basin inter agency committee-Sloan, Playa del Rey small craft harbor, state obligations for highways '48 per state), 1949
    - CUSTOM HOUSE
      - sub-committee- World Trade Committe Special meeting
        (Conference before Civic Center Authority, elimination of structural fire hazards in executive mansion, negotiations- Fed. Government site Custom building, new parcel post building post office garage)
    - PUBLIC WORKS COMMITTEE
      - Public Roads sub-cmmittee S 1305, 1947-48
        (amend federal power act, extension of 1944 Fedral Aid Act, portions of power sites released to states for highway purposes)
      - Public Roads sub-committee H R 1874 2840 AB 46 SB 5 Public Law 601, 1947-48
        (additional bridge between An Francico East Bay metropolitan area, Colliers- Burns highway act '47, construction rural postal routes, Federal Aid highway projects in California, Federal Aid urban highway projects, L A RIVER freeway-analyses of SB 5, map Californiaexprees ways system, map California interstate high way system program, San Francisco Express way system, trans Bay bridge studies, tunnel system Wilmington-San Pedro-Terminal island, system of public streets highways, F Yfderal aid highway program, F Y urban highway program)
    - PUBLIC BUILDINS GROUNDS
      - Sub-commitee P W C H R 3019 3662 H RE 22, 1949
        (activities public buildings administration, bills in bookform, hearins public buildings act, map of locations fedral functions in 1A area unit costs, population of California 1940-48, post office terminal)
    - FLOOD CONTROL
      - Sub-committee P W C H R 5472, 1949
        (Comprehensive plan of flood control L A county drainage basin, flood control approprians bill, flood control report on Santa Anna River tributaries -San Bernardino Riverside counties, Hedger statement, L A County drainage area projects, general flood control program, House documents-fotos clippings), maps of areas, Whittier Narrows dam)
  - File of COMMITTEES, 1950-54
    Arr. aphabetically by Subject of Committee (according to headers) in folders
    - Banking Currency HR 3200 2862 6504 7896 S 2547 3906 Public Law (defense production act) 96 657, 1951, '52 (Box Box COMM. 37)
    - Banking Currency Banking Savings Loan HR 5309 5310 6102 6504 S 2128 2252 3066, 1951-52
    - Banking Currency Currency Stabilization, 1951-52
    - Banking Currency Housing (2 folders) HR 3870 3880 1272 2988 5667 8370 6546 S 349 3066 H CON RES 223 Public Law 94 137 139 547 (L A Public Housing, Defence Housing, reprt Housing Authority of County of L A, 1951-53 1950
    - Banking Currency Price Wage control (prposes re-newall of Defence Production Act, 1951-25 1950
    - Banking Currency Rent Control HR 2051 3871 S 1397 1717 (rent Control Act [UNK], 1951, '52